So, what are we thinking? Poolside
ready. Wow, Cosmo, you're looking really
Wait, where's your swimsuit?
>> I wasn't planning on wearing anything
since I'm always butt naked anyway. But
if you're going to be walking around in
that, I think I'm going to have to cover
up after all.
>> Well, hurry and find something. The line
at the water park is going to be long
with how many are looking to join the
jousting competition.
>> Astro, my phone is ringing. Can you get
that? I'm blowing my insides out on the
toilet.
>> Astron Novalite speaking. Astro.
>> Oh, hi Cosmo. Dandy is going poopy. What
are you calling for?
>> Me and Sprout are heading down to the
pool right now and we were wondering if
Dandy was ready.
>> Did you three make plans?
>> Did Dandy not tell you? There's going to
be a pool noodle jousting competition at
the Garden View Water Park this
afternoon.
>> Oh, no. Dandy doesn't tell me things
because I'm depressed, so I try to make
most things about myself to get false
sympathy.
>> Well, we can't all be loved.
>> Dandy, Cosmo said something about a
jousting competition at the pool. Can I
come?
>> I didn't invite you because you don't
like taking your blanket off, and
there's going to be a lot of tunes
there.
>> I want to be a part of it, too. I'll be
fine with your encouragement.
>> This isn't a game we do for fun, Astro.
Sprout will unal alive you. He takes our
pool noodle jousting competitions way
too far. Here's how it always goes down.
Me and Sprout are the team leaders. We
each choose 10 tunes to be on our side
and then we take turns sending our tunes
out to battle.
>> It sounds serious.
>> It's deadly serious, buddy. The way the
matches work is two tunes stand on a
floaty out in the deep end of the pool
and they try to knock each other off
with pool noodles. Whoever side runs out
of competitors first loses and then the
winning team gets an ice cream pizza
party at the KFC joint Pizza Hut. Full
expenses paid by the losing team, which
is extra punishing as the losing team
usually end up walking away with broken
bones and six figure hospital bills,
too. Golly G. Well, I promised to not
let you down, Dandy.
>> Astro, you came.
>> Dandy told me all about the pool noodle
jousting competition. I may not be
playing a part, but I want to cheer
everybody on and have fun. Are you on
Sprout's team?
>> Well, why wouldn't I be? Sprout is my
boyfriend after all. I I mean best
friend.
>> I'm going to the locker rooms to get
changed.
Oh, Dial, you're in the middle of
changing.
>> Well, it is what the locker room is for.
>> I see you're still rocking the Dandy's
World Educational Center mandated
underwear with my face on it that I used
to force you to wear as part of your
uniform. I'd have thought you stopped
wearing it since we broke up. Well, they
are still high quality undergarments.
So,
>> are you going to join Sprouts team again
this year?
>> That depends on if you are willing to
let me on yours.
I suppose it's a no again this year.
Dandy Cosmo is offering to buy everyone
milkshakes before the competition. Isn't
that so kind?
>> I'm getting bubblegum. Oh, yay. I want
Dubai chocolate.
>> You all wait here. I'll go get them.
>> I'll come help you carry them.
>> What do you want, Astro?
>> I can get one, too.
>> Well, I did say I was treating everyone.
>> Then I want banana fudge.
>> Banana?
That's kind of gay. Hi, Cosmo. Astro,
what can I get for you today? Goob, why
are you working the milkshake stand?
Nobody was here when I got here, so I
climbed in and started role playing. But
I can make yours for realies if you can
talk Sprout into letting me on his team
this year. Cosmo, what do you want?
>> Can we get one bubblegum milkshake and
one Dubai chocolate, one banana nut
fudge?
>> The banana nut kind? Well, okay, but I
don't like the process of having to make
those. That's only three. You're not
getting anything, Cosmo.
>> Me and Sprout always share.
>> You do? Then me and Dandy will share,
too.
>> Uh, are you sure? I don't think Dandy
likes sharing things. One banana nut
fudge coming right up.
>> Hey Goo, we change your mind about the
banana nut fudge.
>> Oh, you couldn't have told me sooner.
Mission accomplished. One bubblegum
milkshake for me and Sprout.
>> And a Dubai chocolate milkshake for the
most special little flower in Garden
View.
>> Stop dancing. We're in public. So, what
if we are? It's embarrassing. You look
like a baby doing a little dance for a
treat.
>> What are you doing?
>> I was just thinking it would be nice to
share.
>> Is it cuz you don't want me to drink at
all? Are you trying to say I'm an ugly
fat [__] like Cosmo?
>> What? No. No, of course not. I mean, you
are a fatty, but I like your pudgginess.
Sometimes I fantasize about using your
belly as a pillow.
>> Oh, well, I don't like sharing things.
>> That's okay. I'll just watch you drink
it.
>> Cosmo, you've got something on your
nose. Oh, what?
Oh, Sprout.
>> Astro, what did you do that for, [__]
>> You had something on your face.
>> Well, yeah. Now I do, [__] I'm done
with my milkshake. I'm going to go jump
in the pool so I can get this off. Don't
follow me.
Hurry the hell up, dweeb. It's time to
pick our teams. I know you brought a lot
of money. I'm looking to get at least
three large supreme pizzas from Pizza
Hut.
Roger Shrimpo, get your fat butt cheeks
over here and make me proud.
Hold on. Why do you get to pick first?
Cuz you already got goob and Cosmo. Then
I pick Poppy for my fourth member.
That's no fair. We said last year that
Poppy's cosmetic bubble tits give her
unfair protective coverage for this type
of game. I don't want to hear that from
someone who has his own natural coverage
by being fat. Then I choose Rudy. You're
only picking him because I pointed out
fat tunes have an unfair advantage.
Yeah, stay mad, Rudy. Get over here, you
fat [__] Damn it. There's no way in
hell any tune here is going to be strong
enough to push Rudy off that damn pool
floaty.
>> Um, what about me?
>> Sweet nibts. Sprout got squirm. Now my
gang of fat [__] I've been
meticulously crafting is going to be
incomplete.
>> Dandy. Dandy pick me. I know how to beat
Squirm.
>> My next pick is Finn. What do you got?
>> I don't really know actually. I just saw
the thickies on your team was piling up
and I'm a bit of a chubby chaser.
>> Dandy. Dandy pick me. I know how to unal
alive a [__]
>> If you really mean that, then get over
here and prove your worth. Tisha, who
else are we thinking? Can my sister
play?
>> If a [__] is called Scraps and doesn't
know how to scrap, what is a [__] even
good for then?
>> Squirm. You're morbidly obese, but
you're right. Scraps. We're giving you a
chance.
>> We've got to go with someone who knows
how to fight, too.
>> Well, then the choice is rather obvious,
I would say.
>> Sylvester, we're still deliberating.
Nobody picked you. Those words have
little value as they leave the lips from
a being with gay colored petals that
surround his head.
>> This is my team.
>> It would be most wise to get that finger
away from my helmet before I remind thee
that the height at which he stands is of
prime height to suck my balls.
Blot. Tegan, step forth. You two shall
accompany us on the road to victory and
[__]
>> Sylvester, stop picking for the whole
team.
Does thou all see how my sword slides
through his form like a hot dog through
a ketchup soaked bun? A being that takes
no damage by being penetrated by a pool
noodle makes for a great and valuable
partner in battle. The same can be said
for Miss Tegan and her porcelain
titties, for they are hard as stone and
will deflect any attack.
>> If they get to pick three, then so do
we. Um, Bassie Brighten me, get over
here, girls.
I thought you were going to pick three.
You just said two.
>> Did I? Well, I don't know how to count
because I'm always distracted by my
boobies because they're always in my
face and there are two of them. So, they
are the only number I know how to count
to.
>> Gordy, you're on my team.
>> Oh, boy.
>> Sprout. I don't know. Gordy is a kid.
>> Yeah, that's why I picked him. Nobody
would hit a child. You underestimate how
many child abusers are living here in
Garden View. Sprout, how many do we have
since Sylvester pulled that little
stunt?
>> Both teams have nine now, which means
this will be our last pick.
>> For my last pick, then
Astro,
>> please, Dandy. I promise you won't
regret it.
>> Boxton, you're with me.
>> Oh,
>> I just don't want my best friend getting
hurt.
>> Yeah, I understand. Thanks for being
honest.
>> Dial, looks like you're on my team again
this year. Dial. So, he is playing after
all.
Hey dial, try not to bore your teammates
with all your useless train facts.
Hey, Dandy. Yeah, what's your team name?
What's yours? We're thinking Sprout and
his Seeds of Malevolence, but we're
waiting to finalize it after we hear
yours cuz we want to make sure ours is
cooler. Any ideas?
>> What about Seeds of Malevolence?
>> That's stealing. He said he didn't
finalize it.
>> Hey, Sprout. What is it, Dork? We talked
it over and we're going with Dandy and
his seeds of malevolence. Dude, what the
hell?
>> Oh, dear God.
>> Cosmo, grab my noodle. I'm talking about
my pool noodle.
I can't watch this. And let the first
match begin. Girly pops.
>> Damn it, Roger. It should have been me.
>> Well, Rudy would have been a better
option, too, since he's used to taking
things up the ass. We are off to a
horrible, horrible start, I'm afraid.
A
>> where the hell did she get a second pool
noodle?
>> I think she snuck it out there by
sticking it up her ass.
Oh no. So did Rudy.
>> It's my turn. Wish me luck. Scraps.
>> Shrimpo, listen to me. We're 0 to2 right
now, which means you've got to get us at
least one point out there. Do you
understand?
>> I don't understand. Crap.
>> Shrimpo, why fight when we can hug
instead? Hugging is gay. I am going to
hurt you very bad. Prepare to face the
fury of my noodle.
>> Silly Shrimpo. If you won't come to me,
then I'll just come to you.
Goob, this isn't the time for hugs. Why
are you smiling, Sprout?
>> Because I know Goob's nature scraps.
That's why I stuck a 14-in steak knife
to his chest fluff when nobody was
looking. Unh.and me, you demonic beast.
I do not desire your hugs.
Shrimpo. Shrimpo.
Everybody huddle up. I just want to say
first off, this is the worst team I have
ever had to be in in my whole entire
life. And I hope you all either die in a
fire or by somebody hitting you in the
head with a hammer.
>> Put me in Dandy. You know I won't let
you down.
>> Tisha, shut up. The competitors are
selected at random. I can't just send
you out there.
I am not going to go up against someone
who weighs the same as an ice cream
truck.
>> You have to, Finn. Those are the rules.
>> Okay, I've got an idea. Let's just send
me out there instead of Finn.
>> Tisha, stop. You are not a bad [__]
Beat his ass, Squirm. Show us all what
you're good for. Look at Finn literally
pissing himself in fear.
Time for us to hop on our own winning
streak, [__]
They're tied. How the hell did they
catch up? Our team was perfect. I can't
believe this.
>> Calm down, Sprout. It's only a game.
It's supposed to be fun.
>> This is going to be the easiest win yet.
That lampshade [__] won't stand a
chance. Are you ready? Blood. Blood.
>> Make Daddy Dandy proud out there,
Boxton. Remember, all you have to do is
kick that pumpkin baby like a football.
Now, what I want you to do is take the
knife and aim for the jugular. You know
what the jugular is, right?
>> Is that what is hanging between boy's
legs? You can aim for that too if you
want. Sprout, you can't be telling him
stuff like that.
>> Stand down, my good [__] for this bout
is mine by right of valor.
>> It's my turn to go out there.
>> A trivial technicality, for fate hath
rewritten the roster.
>> Fate isn't rewriting [__] It's you
who's trying to go out there.
>> This is as much my fight as it is yours.
No. Nay. In fact, it is more so. This is
more my fight than it would ever be
anyone else's.
Hey, what's the holdup?
>> Sir Dandicus, I beseech thee to grant us
a swapping of champions.
>> Uh, I don't know. I would have to talk
to Sprout. Maybe we can allow a one-time
swap if both teams agree. No promises,
though.
>> Um, that's okay. I don't want to play
anymore.
And just like that, we're in the
semifinals. Besties, clap if you've
enjoyed the game so far.
>> Cruel fate. Thou hast robbed me of my
chance to prove my valor before his
gaze. Scared off by the intensity of my
spirit.
>> On team Dandy, we've got Dandy and
Boxton with four points. And on team
Sprout, we have Dial and Sprout's
personal [__] boy, Cosmo, who he has so
many godamn matching skins with in
Dandy's World because they're gay and
everyone knows they're gay. But Quell
can't outright say it because the Roblox
player base is extremely homophobic for
some reason, which she may or may not
have vented to Tamers 1 2 3 4 5 over
Discord on March 12. Now, without
further ado, sexy [__] let's see who
our next challengers are.
>> Oh, I'm going to enjoy this. Cosmo, you
can back out if you want to. I can't.
This is the preliminary rounds. Both
teams have four points. And if I'm
disqualified, just like Gordy, Dandy's
team will be at five. So, the only hope
after that would be a draw. The only way
we can win now is if I beat Dandy.
I sure wish it was you out here, Sprout,
but beating your Swiss roll twink is the
next best thing. Hell, it might even be
more enjoyable seeing your reaction
firsthand at what I do to him.
Oh no, my twink arms are too thin to let
me do any actual physical damage.
Tandy, if you lay one more hand on him.
No hands, then I'll just use my dirty
and stinky feet instead then.
>> Haha. Yay. Go Dandy.
>> I'm going to unal alive you. Dancifer.
Cosmo, get up. Keep throwing. He can't
accuse one of us of cheating if we're
all doing it.
I can't let Sprout down. Not when
everyone's putting in so much effort to
see that I win.
>> He's using the same technique Sprout
used against Roger.
Well, at least you can still give your
team a draw. Box 10.
>> Astro, are you okay over there?
>> Yeah, it's just hot. The game was going
a lot longer than I thought it was going
to go, so I went to McDonald's and got a
Pepsi in the Big Arch.
>> Do you still want to play?
>> The game is coming to a close anyway. I
wouldn't be of much use. Go out there
and get your team your well- earned
draw.
>> Throw me over the big arch for a second,
you pretty little thing.
>> Boxton, are you okay?
>> I'm afraid I diarrhea crapped all over
myself.
>> Well, yeah. That's what happens when you
eat McDonald's.
>> Dandy, there is no way I can continue
like this. Not with so much poopy in my
pants. You have to find a replacement.
What about Astro?
>> Astro, if you're still serious, well,
you'd better get climbing. Dial is
already up there waiting for you.
>> Wait, the final fight is up on the
diving board. It's tradition because it
makes it more exciting when there's the
possibility of a tune actually dying.
You know how many tunes there are that
live in Garden View right now, right?
>> Yeah. Well, there used to be like 10
more.
You really just tried to hurt me, Dial?
>> It is nothing personal. I am just trying
to win the game.
>> Don't you want Dandy to win?
>> Why would I want that?
>> Because Dandy is your friend. I hardly
even see you talk to Sprout.
>> Just because Dandy and I dated before,
it doesn't mean we are friends.
>> Dial isn't even trying to knock him off.
He's just hitting Astro in the face.
>> I get you're jealous that Dandy chose me
to be on his team over you.
>> Actually, Astro, I chose Boxton over you
and you took his spot as a last resort,
but go off, I guess.
>> But you don't have to take it out on me
physically. Dial quit messing with him
and just knocking off so we can go home.
>> I am not jealous of you. I already said
Dandy is a passing acquaintance at most.
Maybe that's why he dumped your ass. Was
it ever real if both of you could drop
each other so easily. Dandy is my friend
first and foremost. It's why if he
doesn't want to be anything more, I'm
fine with it. But it eats away at you
way more than you'd like to admit. You
can't stand that he likes having me
around as a friend while wanting nothing
to do with you. You want me gone so that
Dandy can be sad and alone just like
you. Ah, Astro, I got him.
Goob, don't let go, please.
>> Look, he's wearing tighty whies with
Dandy's face on them. What absolute
[__] material, right? Not like I have
lived experience doing that as well or
anything.
>> What are you doing, Goob? Let him go. He
is the enemy. Oh, RIGHT.
>> Thanks a lot, Astro.
>> We bet our all on you for nothing.
>> Dandy, I think I'm going to be on
Sprout's team next year if that's okay.
Not if I claim an open spot first.
>> Dandy, are you ready to go home? Why are
you crying?
>> Cuz we lost. Duh.
>> Where's the rest of the team? After
giving Sprouts team all the money they
had, half of them went to the hospital
and the other half went to the little
Caesars across the street and scred up
some loose change they had in their
pockets to buy a single pizza so they
can share it and have their own little
pity pizza party. And they didn't let me
go with them cuz they're mad at me.
>> Oh, that's so sad. I'm sorry.
>> I was just so sure I was going to win
this year.
>> If I didn't take Boxton's place, maybe
you would have won.
Yeah, you screwed us all over. But it's
too late now. I'm going home.
What do you want? You're not getting any
pizza, especially after what Flower Boy
did to my Cosmo.
>> I just wanted to give the winner his
gift as a peace offering from Dandy.
>> From the big man himself. Are you
pooping on my butt?
This is the best milkshake I've ever
had.
What flavor is this?
>> I don't know. All I know is that it was
made special. Maybe you should think on
it for a bit.
>> What are these red bits? Astro, what am
I drinking?
>> Ah,
>> Novalite. Novalite. I'll get you for
this.
>> Sprout, what are you screaming for? Come
back to the pizza party.
>> Astro just gave me a strawberry
milkshake.
>> That can't be right. Why would he do
that?
>> It's cuz Astro is mad that we've their
team's so hard that none of them can
even walk straight and he wanted to get
back at me.
>> Gosh. Well, I'm going to go out there
and give Astro a piece of his mind.
>> No. Astro has four arms, which means he
can punch you really easily.
>> Not if we get the drop on him first and
remind him why bakers aren't to be
messed with.
>> What are you saying? I'm saying Astro's
had something a long time coming, and
we're going to wake the neighborhood up
by giving him just what he deserves.
I'm sorry again about losing the game
for us today, Dandy.
>> I already told you we're past that
potato chip.
>> You're really not mad at me,
>> Astro. You're the best pal a little old
flower like me could ask for. Whether
you're good at pool jousting or not,
What's wrong, Astro? Is everything fine?
>> I don't remember leaving the door to my
basement open.
>> Astro. Astro, what's going on?
>> Okay, Dandy, that's enough. You can ease
up on the prank now. Astro, I'm at home.
What do you mean prank?
Ah,
do it, Sprout. Do it. Hit him.
If you're really my best friend, you'll
do it. He joined Dandy's team even after
everyone saw Dandy beating my ass. This
[__] had it coming from the both of us.
Un alive. This [__]
You two are psychos.
Get him. Don't let him get away.
>> Dandy, help me. I can't do anything
right now.
I'm busy.
>> I'm going to die. Dandy.
>> And I just told you I'm busy.
Cosmo.
Are you doing okay?
I think so.
>> Good. I think you deserve an award then.
>> A reward?
Well, my pet does know I like it rough.
like me.
It's funny when we talk that you're
always so nice behind my back and pull
out short.
Do you really have nothing else to do?
I don't give a [__] what you think about
me.
I can't remember what we did last night,
but at least we made it back home.
>> Astro's at the hospital alive. Astro
can't even recall what happened because
he lost so much acre. Last thing he
remembers is leaving the pool. Somebody
beat the actual daylights out of him. Do
you uh think it was a hate crime? Astro
was born wrong so many ways with his
weird forearms, him being gay, having
only like one eye, and [__] He's ugly.
It's hard to pinpoint what exactly the
hate crime could be. So, we're not going
to bother trying to figure it out.
>> Dandy, do you want what's left of my
jello packet?
>> Tell him we're hoping for a speedy
recovery, Dandy. If Astro needs
anything, you let us know.
That was nice of Cosmo offering that,
Dandy. Wouldn't you say?
>> Yeah, sure. Nice.
>> Dandy, I said I'm fine. Tell him thanks
and we can go pick those cookies up
together later. We'll have a batch of
cookies prepared for him as soon as he's
free to leave the hospital.
>> Do it. Hit him. If you're really my best
friend, just do it. This [__] had it
coming from the both of us. Un alive.
This [__]
Hey there, it's me, Sprout Seedley.
How'd you like today's episode of
Dandy's World? Did you think it was
bitching? Don't lie to me. I saw you
staring at my fat ass. Hey, do you see
all these sexy names that scroll by at
the end of Tamer's videos? You can be
one of those names, too. You know, you
just got to subscribe to Tamers 1 2 3 4
5 over on Patreon to show that you
support the good [__] For as low as $3,
your name will be in the credits of all
future episodes, and you can get gifs
from today's episodes and all the
previous ones. But I don't got to tell
you all that since you were planning on
joining his Patreon anyway, right? You
weren't.
Now you listen here, [__] You're going
to subscribe to Tamers 1 2 3 4 5 on
Patreon right now or you and me are
going to have some problems. Yeah, and
he's serious about it, too. Who said
that? I did. Oh, well, stop. I can
handle this myself. So, you and me
aren't going to have any more problems,
right? I want to see your cute little
name at the top of the list in next
week's video. You got that?
>> I don't give a [__] what you think about
me. See all these haters talk, they fly
like me are the only rainy days where
you live.
It's funny when we talk that you're
always so nice. Let me be on my back and
pull our short lives. Do you really have
nothing else to do?
It's always he said that she said that
some
told them rumors that don't bother me.
No, I don't give a [__] what you think
about me. Maybe if you're mad, count to
1, 2, 3. Maybe if you're sad, try to
love me, cuz I don't care anymore.
And so he said that she said that some
told them rumors that don't bother me.
It's always easy that she said that
someone oh told them rumors that don't
bo me.
No, I don't give a [__] what you think
about me. Maybe if you're mad, come to 1
2 3. Maybe if you're sad, try to not
call me. Cuz I don't care anymore. No, I
don't give a [__] what you think about
me. Maybe if you're mad to one, two,
three. Maybe if you're sad, try to not
call me cuz I don't care anymore.